<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pete Jones</title>
    <link>https://www.petejon.es/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pete Jones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 15:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.petejon.es/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>movienetData: A data package for character interactions in popular films.</title>
      <link>https://www.petejon.es/posts/movienetdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.petejon.es/posts/movienetdata/</guid>
      <description>I recently released the data I collected during my PhD research as a data package for R. The main reasons I did this are:
Sharing
One of the most common questions I get when chatting to people at conferences etc. is whether my data is publicly available. I assume this means that people would be interested in taking a look at the data, analysing it, playing around with it and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.petejon.es/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 22:49:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.petejon.es/research/</guid>
      <description>Current projects I recently completed my PhD at the University of Manchester. The thesis is titled &amp;ldquo;A social network analysis approach to examining gendered character positions in popular film narratives&amp;rdquo;. For more info and to take a look at the data and notebooks, check out the project repository.
Publications Jones, Pete. 2018. &amp;ldquo;Diana in the World of Men: a character network approach to analysing gendered vocal representation in Wonder Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.petejon.es/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 16:40:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.petejon.es/contact/</guid>
      <description> Get in touch:    E-mail Github Goodreads Letterboxd LinkedIn ResearchGate Twitter               </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.petejon.es/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 15:50:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.petejon.es/about/</guid>
      <description>Bio I’m a quantitatively trained social scientist currently seeking postdoctoral opportunities having recently completed my PhD at the University of Manchester. My research explores what the relational perspectives and tools of social network analysis can add to our understanding of the narrative marginalisation of women in popular Hollywood cinema.
Education Prior to my PhD, I completed an MSc in Social Research Methods and Statistics and a BA in Social Sciences, both at the University of Manchester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://www.petejon.es/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.petejon.es/license/</guid>
      <description>Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International Creative Commons Corporation (&amp;ldquo;Creative Commons&amp;rdquo;) is not a law firm and does not provide legal services or legal advice. Distribution of Creative Commons public licenses does not create a lawyer-client or other relationship. Creative Commons makes its licenses and related information available on an &amp;ldquo;as-is&amp;rdquo; basis. Creative Commons gives no warranties regarding its licenses, any material licensed under their terms and conditions, or any related information. Creative Commons disclaims all liability for damages resulting from their use to the fullest extent possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>